J. D. Sloan Photographs MS247
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographic prints and negatives, 1978 -- 2013; MS247.001; 7.4 Linear Feet
  - Tufts 2000, MS247.001.005.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Admitted Student Reception, 2000-04-12; MS247.001.005.00002.00034 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000412-Y to 000412-Z
    - 001213-A to 001213-G, 2000-12-13; MS247.001.005.00002.00035 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001213-A to 001213-G
    - Tufts Mort Chair Madoff, 2000-10-17; MS247.001.005.00002.00036 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001017-A to 001017-H
    - Johansen Beck Chair, 2000-11-09; MS247.001.005.00002.00037 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001109-A to 001109-F
    - Tufts: Fan Pier Courthouse M Club Dinner Dance, 2000-11-04; MS247.001.005.00002.00038 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001104-A to 001104-J
    - Tufts Agnes Varis Chair, 2000-12-04; MS247.001.005.00002.00039 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001204-A to 001204-H
  - Tufts 2001-2003, MS247.001.005.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - UCCPS playground Somerville Housing Pierre Omidyar, 2003-05-17; MS247.001.005.00003.00001 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      030517-A to 0030517-L
    - UCCPS playground Somerville Housing Pierre Omidyar, 2003-05-17; MS247.001.005.00003.00002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Theresa Pratt Memorial/CTS Lunch/ Pops, 2001-05-17; MS247.001.005.00003.00003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010517-A to 010517-Q
    - Tufts Karamanlis Chair Greek Opposition, 2001-09-10; MS247.001.005.00003.00004 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010910-A to 010910-K
      Stephen Bosworth; Thanos Veremis; Petros Alivisatos
    - Friedman School Naming, 2001-10-05; MS247.001.005.00003.00005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      011005-A to 011005-V
    - Tufts Food Julie Lampie's Holiday Roast Beef, 2000-12-12; MS247.001.005.00003.00006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      001212-A to 001212-B
    - Tufts Dental Reunion Weekend, 2001-04-28; MS247.001.005.00003.00007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010428-A to 010428-W
    - Tufts Food Julie Lampie's waffle shoot, 2001-05-02; MS247.001.005.00003.00008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010502-A to 010502-D
    - Tufts Medical Senior Awards Dinner, 2001-05-16; MS247.001.005.00003.00009 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010516-A to 010516-H
    - Tufts Dental Assistants, 2001-03-14; MS247.001.005.00003.00010 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010314-A to 010314-E
      Dr. Howard
    - Tommy Hilfiger Tufts Brett & Damon Meyer, 2001-03-07; MS247.001.005.00003.00011 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010307-A to 010307-D
    - Patrons of the Arts / Placido Arango/Helen Franken, 2001-03-29; MS247.001.005.00003.00012 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010329-A to 010329-H
    - Tufts Shapiro Awards, 2001-04-03; MS247.001.005.00003.00013 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010403-A to 010403-D
    - Eaton Computer Lab Dedication, 2001-04-06; MS247.001.005.00003.00014 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010406-Z
    - Tufts Jumbo Club Awards, 2001-04-06; MS247.001.005.00003.00015 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010406-W to 010406-Z
    - Tufts University Awards, 2001-04-06; MS247.001.005.00003.00016 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010406-A to 010406-C
    - Tufts University Frederick Beager Award Demo, 2001-04-10; MS247.001.005.00003.00017 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      010410-A to 010410-B
  - Tufts 2001, MS247.001.005.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Tisch Library Memorial Bench Dedication, 2001-06-28; MS247.001.005.00004.00001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010628-A to 010628-H
    - Tufts Behrakis Dinner, 2001-10-24; MS247.001.005.00004.00002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011024-A to 011024-F
    - Tufts Medical Reunion 2001, 2001-05-12; MS247.001.005.00004.00003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010512-A to 010512-T
    - Tufts MFA Intro Bacows, 2001-10-27; MS247.001.005.00004.00004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011027-A to 011027-K
    - Tufts Vet Barbour Wildlife Opening, 2001-04-23; MS247.001.005.00004.00005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010423-A to 010423-K
    - Tufts Dining Under the Boardwalk Luncheon, 2001-03-13; MS247.001.005.00004.00006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010313-A to 010313-C
    - New Admissions Reception, 2001-04-18; MS247.001.005.00004.00007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010418-A to 010418-B
    - Tufts Dental OKU Dinner, 2001-05-18; MS247.001.005.00004.00008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010518-A to 010518-C
    - Tufts Dental: Dean Norris Golden Crown Awards, 2001-07-13; MS247.001.005.00004.00009 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010713 solo
      School of Dental Medicine; Lonnie Norris
    - Tufts Dental Oral Surgery Graduation @ Anthony's Pier 4, 2001-06-20; MS247.001.005.00004.00010 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010620-A to 010620-C
    - Tufts Dental Bates Andrews Research Dinner, 2001-05-15; MS247.001.005.00004.00011 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010515-A to 010515-D
    - Graduate Awards, 2001-04-30; MS247.001.005.00004.00012 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010430-A to 010430-C
    - Medical School Nicholson Lecture, 2001-05-15; MS247.001.005.00004.00013 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010515-A to 010515-B
    - Luce Luncheon, 2001-05-03; MS247.001.005.00004.00014 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010503-A to 010503-E
    - Tufts: Dental Student National Dental Association Dinner, 2001-05-10; MS247.001.005.00004.00015 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010510-A to 010510-D
    - Tufts Vet Comeback, 2001-10-12; MS247.001.005.00004.00016 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011012-A to 011012-D
    - Tufts Dental Wide Open, 2001-10-01; MS247.001.005.00004.00017 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011001-A to 011001-I
    - Tufts Dental Graduate Periodontal Graduation Dinner, 2001-07-25; MS247.001.005.00004.00018 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010725-A to 010725-C
    - Tufts Dental Prosthodontic Grad Dinner, 2001-07-26; MS247.001.005.00004.00019 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010726-A to 010726-E
    - Tufts Faculty Recognition Dinner, 2001-06-06; MS247.001.005.00004.00020 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010606-A to 010606-D
    - Tufts Anth 1 Portraits Pediatric Grads with Dean, 2001-07-02; MS247.001.005.00004.00021 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010702 solo
      Dr Anthi Tsamsouris
    - Tufts: Friends of Tisch Library Mystery Writers, 2001-11-06; MS247.001.005.00004.00022 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011106 solo
      Michelle Blake; Katherine Hall; Page
    - Tufts Athletics Distinguished Service Awards, 2001-10-26; MS247.001.005.00004.00023 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011026-A to 011026-G
      Bill Richardson; DiBiaggio; Connie Putnam
    - China Pearl Reception, 2001-12-10; MS247.001.005.00004.00024 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011210-A to 011210-C
    - Tufts Pedi 1st Shoot, 2001-11-28; MS247.001.005.00004.00025 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011128-A to 011128-B
    - Tufts Citizenship Poster Session @ Remis Sculpture Court, 2001-10-03; MS247.001.005.00004.00026 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011003-A to 011003-D
    - Tufts: Sci Tech 4 Colby, 2001-09-26; MS247.001.005.00004.00027 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010926-A to 010926-B
    - Tufts Hispanic Food Night Julie Lampie, 2001-10-18; MS247.001.005.00004.00028 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011018-A to 011018-B
    - Tufts: Christopher Columbus Award, 2001-10-18; MS247.001.005.00004.00029 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011018-A to 011018-E
      Tony Cortese; Elaine Ulian; Lou Bertinozzi
    - UEP: Rachel Braatt, 2001-07-12; MS247.001.005.00004.00030 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      010712-A to 010712-C
    - Tufts: Parents Weekend 2001, 2001-10-13; MS247.001.005.00004.00031 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011013-A to 011013-P
    - Tufts Retirement Party for Phil Salem, 2001-12-18; MS247.001.005.00004.00032 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011218-A to 011218-F
    - Tufts: Authors Talk Miriam Nelson Strong Women, 2001-11-27; MS247.001.005.00004.00033 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      011127-A to 011127-B
  - Tufts 1984-2002, MS247.001.005.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Clinton @ Tufts, 2002-03-12; MS247.001.005.00005.00001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      020312-A to 020312-P
    - Clinton @ Tufts, 2002-03-12; MS247.001.005.00005.00002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Mayer Tufts Dental, 1990-04-03; MS247.001.005.00005.00003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      900403 solo
    - Various, 1988-10-01; MS247.001.005.00005.00004 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      881001 D to 881001-F
    - Tufts: Sci/Tech Center Pre-Opening Student Tour, 1990-11-02; MS247.001.005.00005.00005 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Sci/Tech Center Opening, 1990-11-03; MS247.001.005.00005.00006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Commencement, 1988-05-22; MS247.001.005.00005.00007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Groundbreaking Tisch Library, 1994-10-01; MS247.001.005.00005.00008 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      941001-D-7
    - Jean Mayer & Tony Cortese, 1989-03-31; MS247.001.005.00005.00009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      890331-A to 890331-C
    - Canton Engineering Rehab, 1986-01-24; MS247.001.005.00005.00010 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Canton Engineering Rehab, 1986-01-21; MS247.001.005.00005.00011 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Parents Weekend at Tufts, 1990-10-13; MS247.001.005.00005.00012 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Dental, 1990-11-08; MS247.001.005.00005.00013 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - CEM/Kate Philbin, 1988-09-29; MS247.001.005.00005.00014 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Dental, 1988-10-30; MS247.001.005.00005.00015 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Bendetson/Parents Weekend, 1988-10-01; MS247.001.005.00005.00016 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Vet School Sign, 1988-10-16; MS247.001.005.00005.00017 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      881016-A X 2
      contact sheets; Grafton Campus
    - Tufts Designfest, 1987-04-04; MS247.001.005.00005.00018 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Vet School, 1986-12-11; MS247.001.005.00005.00019 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      861211-A to 861121-J
    - Portraits, 1987-03-30; MS247.001.005.00005.00020 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      870330-BB to 870330-OO
    - Fletcher, 1987-04-22; MS247.001.005.00005.00021 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      870422-A to 870422-D
    - Fletcher Commencement, 1984-05-21; MS247.001.005.00005.00022 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      840521-J, D,G,K
    - Tufts Vet, 1989-04-05; MS247.001.005.00005.00023 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Portraits, 1989-09-20; MS247.001.005.00005.00024 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      890920-A to 890920-H
    - MIT, 1988-10-28; MS247.001.005.00005.00025 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Fletcher, 1988-10-29; MS247.001.005.00005.00026 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      881029-A to 881029-F
    - Burk Lab Dental, 1988-04-28; MS247.001.005.00005.00027 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      880428-T to 880428-Z
    - Homecoming 1986, 1986-10-18; MS247.001.005.00005.00028 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - CEM Risk Fibre, 1988-04-28; MS247.001.005.00005.00029 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      880428-A to 880428-F
    - Asbestos, 1988-05-25; MS247.001.005.00005.00030 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Vet Earliest Days, 1984-04-29; MS247.001.005.00005.00031 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - ADA Dental, 1990-10-14; MS247.001.005.00005.00032 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Tufts, 1990-10-19; MS247.001.005.00005.00033 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      901019-A-22A
    - Tufts Nutrition, 1992; MS247.001.005.00005.00034 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Engineering, 1992; MS247.001.005.00005.00035 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Tufts 1990-1991, MS247.001.005.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Dental Color & California, 1991-12-09; MS247.001.005.00006.00001 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911209-A to 911209-D
    - Dr Ernest Clarke Tufts Dental, 1991-11-27; MS247.001.005.00006.00002 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911127-A to 911127-C
    - Tufts: University Wide Dinner Dance, 1991-11-16; MS247.001.005.00006.00003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911116-A to 911116-Z 911116-AA to 911116-II
    - Tufts: Harrison Press Box, 1991-10-26; MS247.001.005.00006.00004 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911026-A to 911026-F
    - Tufts Jumbo Club Smoker!, 1991-10-25; MS247.001.005.00006.00005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911025-A to 911025-I
    - Tufts: Supervisor Training, 1991-10-23; MS247.001.005.00006.00006 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911023-A to 911023-B
      Maria McDonough
    - Tufts: Arts Center Opening, 1991-10-19; MS247.001.005.00006.00007 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911019-A to 911019-Z, 911019-AA to 911019-BB
    - Tufts: Surgeon General Novello N.O.W. Natl Sec, 1991-10-11; MS247.001.005.00006.00008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911011-A to 911011-D
    - Tufts: Mr. Mita receives Honorary Degree, 1991-10-09; MS247.001.005.00006.00009 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911009-A to 911009-E
    - Parents Weekend at Tufts, 1991-10-05; MS247.001.005.00006.00010 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911005-A to 911005-F
    - Tufts: Olin Dinner Dedication, 1991-10-03; MS247.001.005.00006.00011 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911003-A to 911003-I
    - L. Barry Heathrington's shoot of Gaum Fete, 1991-09-20; MS247.001.005.00006.00012 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910920-T to 910920-V
    - Tufts: A T & T Computer Grant, 1991-09-12; MS247.001.005.00006.00013 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910912-A
    - Tufts Dental: Prophylaxis, 1991-07-20; MS247.001.005.00006.00014 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910720 solo
    - Tufts Dental: Noble Farmer Reception, 1991-06-26; MS247.001.005.00006.00015 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910626-A to 910626-D
    - Tufts Engineering Dean Nelson, 1991-05-03; MS247.001.005.00006.00016 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910503 solo
    - Tufts Art Center, 1991-10-19; MS247.001.005.00006.00017 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      911019-YY to 911019-ZZ
    - Tufts Dental Mark Gonthier, 1991-06-14; MS247.001.005.00006.00018 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910614-A to 910614-O
    - Tufts Dental, 1991-06-11; MS247.001.005.00006.00019 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910611-A to 910611-C
    - Misc: Advisees at Graduation, 1991-06-07; MS247.001.005.00006.00020 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910607 solo
    - Carole Boulter Medical Alumni, 1991-06-01; MS247.001.005.00006.00021 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910601-A to 910601-N
    - Sackler Tufts, 1991-05-30; MS247.001.005.00006.00022 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910530 solo
    - Tufts Medical School Senior Dinner, 1991-05-08; MS247.001.005.00006.00023 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910508-A to 910508-I
    - Tufts, 1991-05-10; MS247.001.005.00006.00024 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910510-A to 910510-C
    - Tufts Employee Recognition, 1991-04-25; MS247.001.005.00006.00025 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910425-A to 910425-B
    - Tufts Color: Aidekman Arts Ctr, 1991-04-24; MS247.001.005.00006.00026 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910424-A to 910424-E
    - Tufts Dental Alumni, 1991-04-20; MS247.001.005.00006.00027 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910420-A to 910420-P
    - Tufts Dental Kayer Clinic, 1991-04-19; MS247.001.005.00006.00028 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910419-A to 910419-E
    - Tufts, 1991-04-18; MS247.001.005.00006.00029 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910418 solo
    - Tufts Dental Prosthedontics, 1991-04-12; MS247.001.005.00006.00030 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910412-A to 910412-B
    - Olin Lang Bldg & Raytheon Gift, 1991-03-26; MS247.001.005.00006.00031 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910326 solo
      Diane Krieger
    - Tufts Engineering, 1991-03-25; MS247.001.005.00006.00032 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910325-A to 910325-D
    - Aidekman Arts Center & Dormitory, 1991-03-15; MS247.001.005.00006.00033 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910315 solo
    - Tufts Dental Restorative, 1991-03-08; MS247.001.005.00006.00034 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910308-A to 910308-E
    - Tufts Dental: Friends of Gino Passamonte, 1991-01-17; MS247.001.005.00006.00035 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      910117-A to 910117-H
    - Tufts: Balsa Bridge, 1990-12-03; MS247.001.005.00006.00036 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      901203-A to 901203-D
    - Medical Talent Show, 1990-12-01; MS247.001.005.00006.00037 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      901201-A to 901201-G
      School of Medicine; Marge Dwyer; Carole Boulter
  - Bacow Inauguration, 2002-04-19 -- 2002-04-20; MS247.001.005.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Bacow Inauguration, 2002-04-19; MS247.001.005.00007.00001 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      020419-A to 020419-T
    - Bacow Inauguration, 2002-04-19; MS247.001.005.00007.00002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      020419-A to 020419-S
    - Bacow Inauguration, 2002-04-20; MS247.001.005.00007.00003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      020420-A to 020420-O
    - Bacow Inauguration, 2002-04-20; MS247.001.005.00007.00004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Al Gore; George Bush; Desmond Tutu, 1994 -- 2003; MS247.001.006.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Al Gore, 2002-01-25; MS247.001.006.00001.00001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      020125-A to 020125-M
    - Al Gore @ Tufts, 2002-01-25; MS247.001.006.00001.00002 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Dr Lerner
    - Al Gore and girls, 2002-01-25; MS247.001.006.00001.00003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      020125-M
      photographic prints; Medford Campus
    - Al Gore, Bacow's Elise Renoni, 2002-01-25; MS247.001.006.00001.00004 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      020125-24A
    - Al Gore Bacow's and Sally Kiely, 2002-01-25; MS247.001.006.00001.00005 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      020125-27A
    - Al Gore and Deborah Bobek, 2002-01-25; MS247.001.006.00001.00006 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      020125-J 14A
    - George Bush, 2003-02-26; MS247.001.006.00001.00007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      030226-A to 030226-K
    - George HBW Bush, Mitt Romney 2003 Fares Lecture, 2003-02-26; MS247.001.006.00001.00008 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - George Bush @ Tufts, 1994-10-25; MS247.001.006.00001.00009 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      941025-A to 941025-R
    - Archbishop Desmond Tutu, 2002-04-12; MS247.001.006.00001.00010 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      020412-A
  - Tufts 2004, MS247.001.006.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Patricia Campbell's Goodbye Tufts Dental, 2004-12-08; MS247.001.006.00002.00001 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      041208: 467-471
    - Tufts: U.College Mock Pres. Debate, 2004-10-28; MS247.001.006.00002.00002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      041028: 168-172
      Roberta Oster Sachs
    - Hillary Clinton @ Tufts, 2004-11-10; MS247.001.006.00002.00003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      041110: 3077-3080
    - Tufts: 1st Faculty Advancement Ceremony "Tenured Faculty", 2004-11-18; MS247.001.006.00002.00004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      041118: 398-400
    - Tufts: Locally grown apples, 2004-10-21; MS247.001.006.00002.00005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      041021: 127-130
    - Opening of the Dranetz Tower, 2004-09-08; MS247.001.006.00002.00006 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040908: 055-058
    - Tufts Dental: Opening Day, 2004-08-31; MS247.001.006.00002.00007 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040831: 469-477
    - Tufts Dental Foreign Student White coat ceremony, 2004-09-07; MS247.001.006.00002.00008 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040907: 2999-3000
    - Tufts Medical Distinguished Service, 2004-05-03; MS247.001.006.00002.00009 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040503-A to 040503-B
    - Tufts Commencement Honorary Degree Dinner, 2004-05-22; MS247.001.006.00002.00010 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040522:611-618
    - Tufts Rock's Non Smoke Kerrigan & Hammond, 1994-10-21; MS247.001.006.00002.00011 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      941021-V
    - Tufts: Berger Demos, 2004-04-29; MS247.001.006.00002.00012 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040429: 450-452
    - Tufts Dental: Bates / Andrews Dinner, 2004-05-06; MS247.001.006.00002.00013 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040506: 889 & 890
    - Tufts: Ortho Dept Dr. Briss, 2004-06-01; MS247.001.006.00002.00014 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040601 solo
    - Tufts Night at the Pops, 2004-05-20; MS247.001.006.00002.00015 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040520: 981-984
    - Tufts: UCCPS Presidential Awards, 2004-04-14; MS247.001.006.00002.00016 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040414: 599-602
    - Dr Barry Briss, 2004-05-18; MS247.001.006.00002.00017 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040518: 483-484
    - Dr Barry Briss, 2004-05-18; MS247.001.006.00002.00018 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Tufts Jumbo Awards, 2004-04-03; MS247.001.006.00002.00019 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040403: 91-95
    - Tufts Shapiro Awards, 2004-03-30; MS247.001.006.00002.00020 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040330:19-20
    - Tisch Library "Mirror Mirror" Author Talk Gregory Maguire, 2004-03-10; MS247.001.006.00002.00021 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040310-A to 040310-B
    - Mardi Gras Night Julie Lampie, 2004-02-24; MS247.001.006.00002.00022 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040224:A643-D646
    - Tufts Dental Bates/Andrews Poster Session, 2004-03-03; MS247.001.006.00002.00023 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040303-A to 040303-F
    - UCCPS Poster Session, 2004-03-03; MS247.001.006.00002.00024 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040303-U to 040303-Z
    - Yankee Dental, 2004-01-30; MS247.001.006.00002.00025 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      040130-A to 040130-F
  - Tufts 2004 Volume 2, MS247.001.006.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dental Reunion, 2004; MS247.001.006.00003.00001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      3355-3373
    - University College, 2004-04-26; MS247.001.006.00003.00002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      040426-A345
    - 1890-1893, 2004; MS247.001.006.00003.00003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      1890-1893
    - Robing and Stage, 2004-05-23; MS247.001.006.00003.00004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      040523:739-743
      Judy Olson
    - UCCPS Volunteer Day, 2004-05-22; MS247.001.006.00003.00005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      040522:6835-6840
    - Parents Program, 2004-05-22; MS247.001.006.00003.00006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      040522:6833-6834
    - Clean Tufts, 2004-05-20; MS247.001.006.00003.00007 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      040520:6868-6569
    - Hooding, 2004-05-22; MS247.001.006.00003.00008 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      040522:6955-6958
    - White coat ceremony, 2004-03-26; MS247.001.006.00003.00009 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      040326:21-35
    - Tommy Bahama Beach Theme Dental Dinner, 2004; MS247.001.006.00003.00010 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      3166-3172
    - Tufts Medical Reunion, 2004; MS247.001.006.00003.00011 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      6154-6172
  - Tufts 2002-2004, MS247.001.006.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Medical Dean & Wife Portrait, 2004-05-22; MS247.001.006.00004.00001 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      040522 roll
    - Tufts Tisch, 2004; MS247.001.006.00004.00002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      3248-3252
    - 19th Annual Vet Alumni Reunion & Comeback, 2004-08-07; MS247.001.006.00004.00003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      5156-5162
    - Vet Comeback @ Sheraton, 2002-09-13; MS247.001.006.00004.00004 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      020913-A to 020913-G
    - Vet Comeback @ Sheraton, 2002-09-13; MS247.001.006.00004.00005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Tufts 2002, MS247.001.006.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Parents Weekend, 2002-10-18; MS247.001.006.00005.00001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      021018-A to 021018-M
    - Tufts Dental Rededication of the pain center, 2002-10-25; MS247.001.006.00005.00002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      021025-A to 021025-F
    - Dental Musicians, 2002-06-20; MS247.001.006.00005.00003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020620 solo
    - Tufts Dental white coat ceremony, 2002-03-25; MS247.001.006.00005.00004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020325-A to 020325-H
    - DiBiaggio Chair, 2002-02-07; MS247.001.006.00005.00005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020207-A to 020207-M
    - Tufts dental Pedo Grad, 2002-07-23; MS247.001.006.00005.00006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020723 solo
    - Tufts: Perio Dinner, 2002-07-24; MS247.001.006.00005.00007 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020724-A to 020724-E
    - Tufts-Rebuilding Afghanistan/Fletcher, 2002-04-29; MS247.001.006.00005.00008 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020429-A to 020429-D
      Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Andrew Natsios
    - Tufts: Graduate School Awards, 2002-04-29; MS247.001.006.00005.00009 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020429-W to 020429-Z
      Robin Kanarek
    - Tufts: Natalie Zucher Chair, 2002-04-10; MS247.001.006.00005.00010 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020410-A to 020410-G
    - Archbishop Desmond Tutu, 2002-04-12; MS247.001.006.00005.00011 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020412-A to 020412-B
    - Friedman School Stanley N. Gershoff Chair, 2002-04-09; MS247.001.006.00005.00012 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020409-A to 020409-H
    - Tufts: Shapiro Awards, 2002-04-03; MS247.001.006.00005.00013 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020403-A to 020403-C
    - Tufts: 2000 UCCPS Presidential Awards, 2002-04-12; MS247.001.006.00005.00014 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020412-A to 020412-D
    - Tufts Neubauer Scholars Dinner, 2002-04-12; MS247.001.006.00005.00015 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Dental: Matthew Hand Research NIH phenom, 2002-04-18; MS247.001.006.00005.00016 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020418-Z
    - Tufts: Eric Johnson Focus Group, 2002-04-02; MS247.001.006.00005.00017 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020402 solo
    - Greek Orthodox Patriarch Gift of Big Book and Adele Bacow family, 2002-04-17; MS247.001.006.00005.00018 (Box 6, Folder 5)